{
    "subject": "resource/Der_bewegte_Mann",
    "predicate": "property/producer",
    "object": "resource/Bernd_Eichinger",
    "human_readable": "Der bewegte Mann was produced by Bernd Eichinger.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9741368293762207,
            "question": "What was the role of Bernd Eichinger in the production of 'Der bewegte Mann'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8778457641601562,
            "question": "Who produced the film 'Der bewegte Mann'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.839050829410553,
            "question": "Name a film produced by Bernd Eichinger."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8363788723945618,
            "question": "Besides 'Der bewegte Mann', what other works are associated with Bernd Eichinger?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8102427124977112,
            "question": "Who was responsible for producing the film 'Der bewegte Mann'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7251220345497131,
            "question": "What is the name of the film producer who worked on 'Der bewegte Mann'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6525293588638306,
            "question": "Is Bernd Eichinger known for producing films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5738677978515625,
            "question": "Can you tell me about any other films produced by Bernd Eichinger?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5621078610420227,
            "question": "Was Bernd Eichinger involved in the making of any notable films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5227078795433044,
            "question": "What is known about Bernd Eichinger's career in film production?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Der bewegte Mann was produced by Bernd Eichinger.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6910_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Bernd Eichinger involved in the making of any notable films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6910_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about any other films produced by Bernd Eichinger?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6910_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Bernd Eichinger known for producing films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6910_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6910_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6910_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6910_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6910_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6910_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6910_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6910_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6910_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6910_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6910_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information about the film \"Der bewegte Mann\" and mention that it was produced by Bernd Eichinger, which aligns with the statement given in the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}